Finding Aid for the A&M Records Records PASC-M.0269
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sound recordings, 1910-1999; Series 12.
  - Commercial cassette and 8-track tapes, Subseries 4.; 26 items
    - Keep Your Eye On Me, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: CS 5125
      Two copies.
    - Under a Spanish Moon, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: CS 5209
    - Greatest Hits/Greatest Stars = Grands Succes/Meilleurs Artistes, 1977; 2 8- track tapes (Box 59, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.:
    - What Now My Love, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: CS 4114
    - Herb Alpert's Ninth, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: CS 4134
    - The Brass Are Coming, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: CS 4228
    - Sounds Like, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: CS 4124
    - S.R.O., 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: CS 4119
    - The Beat Of The Brass, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: CS 4146
    - Greatest Hits, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: CS 4245
    - Solid Brass, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: CS 4341
    - Going Places, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: CS 4112
    - The Hits, 4 sound cassettes (Box 59, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: EC 50008
    - England Dan and John Ford Coley, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: CS 4305
      Also performed by: John Ford Coley.
    - Apasionado, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: 75021 5297 4
    - Last Of The Runaways, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: CS 5272
    - Sun Down Lady, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: CS 4359
    - Seasons, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: CS 3033
    - Smackwater Jack, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: CS 3037
    - The Age Of Steam (Box 65, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: CS 3036
      Cassette container only.
    - I'm A Believer, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 23)
      Publisher no.: WC 8429
    - Spooky Two, 1 sound cassette (Box 65, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: CS 4194
  - Commercial classical music: 33 1/3 rpm LP sound recordings, Subseries 5.
    - Gayne--Ballet suite, 1 12" sound disc (Box 42, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: 12498-D
    - The World Of Red Seal Digital, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: XRC1-3624
      Performed by: Emanuel Ax, James Levine, Eduardo Mata, and Eugene Ormandy.
    - [Selections], 1 12" sound disc (Box 47, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: 1112 3577
      Te Deum -- 149th Psalm -- Hymnus.
    - Satyagraha, 1 12" sound disc (Box 60, Folder 2)
      3 discs and booklet
    - The Complete String Quartets, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 61, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: ARL 3-3834
      Box set of the complete string quartets by Brahms and Schumann.
    - Ma Vlast, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: 1110 3431-2 ZA
      Box set.
    - A Music Box Christmas (Box 170, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: CS 8498
      Silent Night, Holy Night -- Hark! The Herald Angels Sing -- Zu Bethlehem Geboren -- The Monastery Bells -- O Tannenbaum -- O Sanctissima -- Spin, Spin -- O Holy Night -- Ave Maria -- Adeste Fidelis -- Still, Still, Holy Melody -- Jesus, Lover of My Soul -- The First Noel -- Ihr Kinderlein Kommet -- The Holy City -- Lobe den Herren -- Jingle Bells -- Silent Night, Holy Night.
    - The Six Early Quartets, op. 18, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: ARL 3-3486
      Box set
    - Carmen, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: ARL1-3343
    - [Orchestral Works], 1980 (Box 46, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: ARL1-3640
      Symphony in C --L'Arlesienne Suite No.1.
    - The Complete Caruso, vol.8, 1910-1911, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 46, Folder 32)
      Publisher no.: ARM1-3570
    - The Complete Caruso, vol.9, 1911-1912, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 46, Folder 31)
      Publisher no.: ARM1-3571
    - Mame, A New Musical (Box 170, Folder 1)
      Overture -- St. Bridget -- It's Today -- Open A New Window -- The Man In the Moon -- My Best Girl -- We Need A Little Christmas -- Mame -- The Letter -- Bosom Buddies - Gooch's Song -- That's How Young I Feel -- If He Walked Into My Life -- Finale.
    - West Side Story, the original sound track recording (Box 170, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: OL 5670
      Prologue -- Jet Song -- Something's Coming -- Dance at the Gym -- Maria -- America -- Tonight -- Gee, Officer Krupke! -- I Feel Pretty -- One Hand, One Heart -- Quintet -- The Rumble -- Cool -- A Boy Like That and I Have A Love -- Somewhere (Finale).
    - Clementi Sonatas: Op.34 No.2, Op.14 No.3, Op.26 No.2, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 46, Folder 30)
      Publisher no.: ARM1-3689
      A recording in "The Horowitz Collection."
    - I Am the Blues (Box 170, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: CS 9987
      Back Door Man -- I Can't Quit You, Baby -- The Seventh Son -- Spoonful -- I Ain't Superstitious -- You Shook Me -- I'm Your Hoochie Coochie Man -- The Little Red Rooster -- The Same Thing.
    - J.S. Bach Preludes (Box 44, Folder 9)
      Also performed by: Olgerts Cintins.
    - Ormandy Conducts Dvorak, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: ARL1-3555
      Symphony No.7.
      Conducted by Eugene Ormandy.
    - Symphony No.8 in G, Op.88, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: ARL1-3550
    - Don't Go To Strangers (Box 170, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: CS 9276
      How About Me -- What's New -- What Did I Have That I Don't Have? -- I'll Be Around -- If He Walked Into My Life -- Don't Go To Strangers -- I Wish You Love -- How Did He Look -- I Wanna Be Around -- Tell Him I Said Hello -- When He Leaves You.
    - Samson, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: ARL4-3635
      Performed by Janet Baker, Helen Watts, Robert Tear, John Shiley-Quirk, and Benjamin Luxon. Box set.
    - String quartets: Op.20, No.4 in D & Op.74, No.3 in G Minor, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: ARL1-3485
    - The Graduate, the original sound track recording (Box 170, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: OS 3180
      Sounds of Silence -- The Singleman Party Foxtrot -- Mrs. Robinson -- Sunporch Cha-Cha-Cha -- Scarborough Fair/Canticle (Interlude) -- On the Strip -- April Come She Will -- The Folks -- Scarborough Fair/Canticle -- The Great Effect -- The Big Bright Green Pleasure Machine -- Whew -- Mrs. Robinson -- Sounds of Silence.
      Additional music by David Grusin.
    - The Second Barbara Streisand Album, 1963 (Box 170, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: CS 8854
      Any Place I Hang My Hat Is Home -- Right as the Rain -- Down With Love -- Who Will Buy? -- When the Sun Comes Out -- Gotta Move -- My Coloring Book -- I Don't Care Much -- Lover, Come Back To Me -- I Stayed Far Too Long at the Fair -- Like a Straw in the Wind.
  - Commercial popular music: 33 1/3 rpm LP sound recordings, Subseries 6.
    The series is arranged alphabetically by performer.
    - The Prince's Trust 10th Anniversary Birthday Party, 1 12" sound disc (Box 32, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: AMA 3906
    - A Very Special Christmas, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: SP 3911
    - Christopher Plummer as Cyrano, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 39, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: SP 6504
    - They Come to America, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: WR 98334
    - World Star Festival, 1 12" sound disc (Box 42, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: CSS 867
    - Halloween Horrors, 1977; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: SP 3300
      Side One: Story, Halloween Horror. Side Two: The sounds of Halloween and other useful effects.
    - A Song For You, 1972; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: SP 3511
      A Song For You / Leon Russell -- Top Of the World / Richard Carpenter and John Bettis -- Hurting Each Other / Peter Udell and Gary Geld -- It's Going To Take Some Time / Carole King and Toni Stern -- Goodbye To Love / Richard Carpenter and John Bettis -- Intermission / Richard Carpenter -- Bless the Beasts and Children / Barry DeVorzon and Perry Botkin, Jr. -- Flat Baroque / Richard Carpenter -- Piano Picker / Randy Edelman -- I Won't Last A Day Without You / Paul Williams and Roger Nichols -- Crystal Lullaby / Richard Carpenter and John Bettis -- Road Ode / Gary Sims and Dan Woodhams -- A Song For You / Leon Russell.
    - The Singles, 1969-1973, 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: SP 3601
      We've Only Just Begun -- Top Of the World -- Ticket To Ride -- Superstar -- Rainy Days and Mondays -- Goodbye To Love -- Yesterday Once More -- It's Going To Take Some Time -- Sing -- For All We Know -- Hurting Each Other -- (They Long To Be) Close To You.
    - Burt Bacharach's Greatest Hits, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: SP 3661
      I'll Never Fall In Love Agaian -- Make It Easy On Yourself -- This Guy's In Love With You -- Reach Out For Me -- The Look Of Love -- What the World Needs Now Is Love -- I Say A Little Prayer -- Alfie -- Raindrops Keep Fallin' On My Head -- Wives & Lovers -- (They Long To Be) Close To You -- Living Together, Growing Together.
    - Made In America, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: SP 3723
      Those Good Old Dreams -- Strength Of A Woman -- (Want You) Back In My Life Again -- When You've Got What It Takes -- Somebody's Been Lyin' -- I Believe You -- Touch Me When We're Dancing -- When It's Gone (It's Just Gone) -- Beechwood 4-5789 -- Because We Are In Love (The Wedding Song).
    - Reflector, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: SP 3726
      This Time -- Cool Love -- Don't Let the Magic Disappear -- One More Night -- Jenny -- Slip Away -- That's When -- Inside/Outside -- Paradise (Let Me Take You Into) -- Drums In the Night.
    - Footsteps In the Dark, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: SP 3736
      The Wind -- (I Never Wanted) To Be A Star -- Katmandu -- I Want To Live In A Wigwam -- Trouble -- On the Road To Find Out -- If You Want To Sing Out, Sing Out -- Where Do the Children Play? -- Daytime -- Don't Be Shy -- How Can I Tell You -- Father and Son -- The Hurt -- Silent Sunlight.
    - The Dream of the Blue Turtles, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: SP 3750
      If You Love Somebody Set Them Free -- Love Is the Seventh Wave -- Russians -- Children's Crusade -- Shadow's In the Rain -- We Work the Black Seam -- Consider Me Gone -- The Dream Of the Blue Turtles -- Moon Over Bourbon Street -- Fortress Around Your Heart.
    - The Collection, 1986 (Box 173, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: SP 3900
      Stay For Awhile -- Find A Way -- Everywhere I Go -- Angels -- El Shaddai -- Love Can Do -- Sing Your Praise To the Lord -- Father's Eyes -- Thy Word -- Emmanuel.
    - Whipped Cream and Other Delights (Box 173, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: SP 4110
      A Taste of Honey -- Green Peppers -- Tangerine -- Bittersweet Samba -- Lemon Tree -- Whipped Cream -- Love Potion No. 9 -- El Garbanzo -- Ladyfingers -- Butterball -- Peanuts -- Lollipops and Roses.
    - For Animals Only, 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: SP 4113
      For Animals Only -- Puff (The Magic Dragon) -- Elephant Soul -- Gnu Bossa Nova -- Last of the Red Hot Llamas -- La Cucaracha -- How Much Is That Doggie In the Window -- Yellow Bird -- Swan Waltz -- A Partridge In A Pear Tree (The Twelve Days of Christmas) -- El Gazelle -- Las Mananitas.
    - Sounds Like.., 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: SP 4124
      Gotta Lotta Livin' To Do -- Lady Godiva -- Bo-Bo -- Shades Of Blue -- In A Little Spanish Town -- Wade In the Water -- Town Without Pity -- The Charmer -- Treasure Of San Miguel -- Miss Frenchy Brown -- Casino Royale.
    - Reach Out, 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: SP 4131
      Reach Out For Me -- Alfie -- Bond Street -- Are You There (With Another Girl) -- What the World Needs Now Is Love -- The Look Of Love -- A House Is Not A Home -- I Say A Little Prayer -- The Windows Of the World -- Lisa -- Message To Michael.
    - River Deep - Mountain High, 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: SP 4178
      River Deep-Mountain High -- I Idolize You -- A Love Like Yours -- A Fool In Love -- Make 'Em Wait -- Hold On Baby -- I'll Never Need More Than This -- Save the Last Dance For Me -- Oh Baby! -- Every Day I Have To Cry -- Such A Fool For You -- It's Gonna Work Out Fine.
      Produced by Phil Spector.
    - Make It Easy On Yourself, 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: SP 4188
      Promises, Promises -- I'll Never Fall In Love Again -- Knowing When To Leave -- Any Day Now -- Wanting Things -- Whoever You Are I Love You -- Make It Easy On Yourself -- Do You Know the Way To San Jose -- Pacific Coast Highway -- She's Gone Away -- This Guy's In Love With You.
    - Greatest Hits, 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: SP 4245
      Lonely Bull -- Spanish Flea -- Getting Sentimental Over You -- Love Potion #9 -- Never On Sunday -- Mexican Shuffle -- Taste Of Honey -- Tijuana Taxi -- South Of The Border -- America -- Whipped Cream -- Zorba The Greek.
      A second copy is in the same box, item #20.
    - Greatest Hits, 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 20)
      A second copy is in the same box, item #19.
    - Greatest Hits, 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: SP 4248
      Comin' In The Back Door -- Yours -- Along Comes Mary -- Spanish Eyes -- Fowl Play -- The Look Of Love -- Georgy Girl -- Ghost Riders In The Sky -- Acapulco 1922 -- Some Where My Love -- Maria Elena -- Brasilia.
    - Close To You, 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: SP 4271
      We've Only Just Begun -- Love Is Surrender -- Maybe It's You -- Reason To Believe -- Help -- Close To You -- Baby It's You -- I'll Never Fall In Love Again -- Crescent Noon -- Mr. Guder -- I Kept On Loving You -- Another Song.
    - Storm at Sunup, 1975; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 23)
      Publisher no.: SP 4533
      Storm at Sunup -- Love Me Now -- Mama Coco -- Father and Son -- Where Am I Going -- Keep on Walking -- Love is a Night -- Gettin' High.
    - Main Squeeze, 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: SP 4612
      (the day after) our first night together -- if you know me any longer than tomorrow -- love the feelin' -- i get crazy (when your eyes touch mine) -- doin' everything with you -- main squeeze.
    - Sounds.., 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: SP 4685
      Stuff Like That -- I'm Gonna' Miss You In The Morning -- Love, I Never Had It So Good -- Tell Me A Bedtime Story -- Love Me By Name -- Superwoman (Where Were You When I Needed You) -- Takin' It To The Streets.
    - Sounds.., 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 25)
    - Sad Cafe, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 26)
      Publisher no.: SP 4737
      Restless -- Here Come The Clowns -- Run Home Girl -- Black Rose -- I Believe (Love Will Survive) -- Babylon -- Shellshock -- Hungry Eyes -- Feel Like Dying -- On With The Show.
    - I Could Have Been A Sailor, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: SP 4789
      I Could Have Been A Sailor -- Don't Wish Too Hard -- Two Boys -- Angels With Dirty Faces -- Don't Cry Out Loud -- If You Were Wondering -- Don't Leave Me Now -- I'd Rather Leave While I'm In Love -- We've Come To An Understanding -- Paris At 21.
    - You Want It - You Got It, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 28)
      Publisher no.: SP 4864
      Lonely Nights -- One Good Reason -- Don't Look Now -- Coming Home -- Fits Ya Good -- Jealousy -- Tonight -- You Want It, You Got It -- Last Chance -- No One Makes It Right.
    - Night And Day, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 29)
      Publisher no.: SP 4906
      Another World -- Chinatown -- T.V. Age -- Target -- Steppin' Out -- Breaking Us In Two -- Cancer -- Real Men -- A Slow Song.
    - Mike's Murder, 1983; 1 12" sound trac (Box 173, Folder 30)
      Publisher no.: SP 4931
      Cosmopolitan -- 1-2-3-Go (This Town's A Fairground) -- Laundromat Monday -- Memphis -- Moonlight -- Zemio -- Breakdown -- Moonlight Theme.
      A Motion Picture Soundtrack
    - Stay With Me Tonight, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 31)
      Publisher no.: SP 4940
      Don't You Get So Mad -- We're Going All The Way -- Stay With Me Tonight -- Greatest Love Affair -- Plane Love -- Other Side Of The Coin -- I'll Make Believe -- When Are You Comin' Back? -- Forever Mine -- Two Wrongs Don't Make A Right.
    - Voice Of The Heart, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 32)
      Publisher no.: SP 4954
      Now -- Sailing On The Tide -- You're Enough -- Make Believe It's Your First Time -- Two Lives -- At The End Of A Song -- Ordinary Fool -- Prime Time Love -- Your Baby Doesn't Love You Anymore -- Look To Your Dreams.
    - Junge Roemer, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 33)
      Publisher no.: SP 4993
      Junge Roemer -- Tut-Ench-Amon (Tutankhamen) -- Brillantin' Brutal -- Ihre Tochter -- No Answer -- Nur Mit Dir -- Hoch Wie Nie -- Kann Es Liebe Sein.
    - Brother Where You Bound, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 34)
      Publisher no.: SP 5014
      Cannonball -- Still In Love -- No Inbetween -- Better Days -- Brother Where You Bound -- Ever Open Door.
    - As The Band Turns, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 35)
      Publisher no.: SP 5019
      Freak-A-Ristic -- Cool, Calm, Collected -- One Love -- In The Heat Of Passion -- If Your Heart Isn't In It -- Silver Shadow -- Let's Start It Over -- Secret Lovers -- Thank You.
    - 2000 And Thirteen, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: BS 2741
      Will To Live -- Slow Growth -- Natural Foods -- Phil -- Asparagus -- Origin Of Words -- Great Inventions -- Strawberries -- Miracle Fruits -- The Greatest Invention -- Ancient Poetry -- The Fig Leaf -- Paul Revere -- Ma And Pa -- Jesus And The Apostles -- Generals -- Winston Churchill -- War Of The Roses -- Dolly Madison -- Lord Byron -- 21,000 Doctors -- Jolson -- America's Economic Plight -- Hope For Mankind.
    - In Flight, 1977; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: BSK 2983
      Nature Boy -- The Wind And I (AKA Hotstuff) -- The World Is A Ghetto -- Gonna Love You More -- Valdez In The Country -- Everything Must Change.
    - Breezin', 1976; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: BS 2919
      Breezin' -- This Masquerade -- Six To Four -- Affirmation -- So This Is Love? -- Lady.
    - Weekend In L.A., 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: 2WB 3139
      The Greatest Love Of All -- Down Here On The Ground -- Ode To A Kudu -- We As Love -- California P.M. -- Lady Blue -- We All Remember Wes -- Windsong -- On Broadway -- It's All In The Game -- Weekend In L.A.
    - Livin' Inside Your Love, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: 2BSK 3277
      Livin' Inside Your Love -- Hey Girl -- Nassau Day -- Soulful Strut -- Prelude To Fall -- A Change Is Gonna Come -- Love Ballad -- You're Never Too Far From Me -- Love Is A Hurtin' Thing -- Welcome Into My World -- Before You Go -- Unchained Melody.
    - Gorilla, 1975; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: RS 2866
      Mexico -- Music -- How Sweet It Is (To Be Love By you) -- Wandering -- Gorilla -- You Make It Easy -- I Was A Fool To Care -- Lighthouse -- Angry Blues -- Love Songs -- Sarah Maria.
    - Mirage A Trois, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: 23813-1
      Claire's Song -- Top Secret -- I Got Rhythm -- Pass It On -- Goin' Home -- Man In The Moon -- Elamar -- Nimbus.
    - Hearts and Bones, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: 23942-1
      Allergies -- Hearts And Bones -- When Numbers Get Serious -- Think Too Much (b) -- Song About The Moon -- Think Too Much (a) -- Train In The Distance -- Rene And Georgette Magritte With Their Dog After The War -- Cars Are Cars -- The Late Great Johnny Ace.
    - Yellow Jackets, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: 25Z04-1
      Homecoming -- Deat Beat -- Daddy's Gonna Miss You -- Sylvania -- Silverlake -- Lonely Weekend -- Los Mambos -- Samurai Samba.
    - Double Vision, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: 25393-1
      Maputo -- More Than Friends -- Moon Tune -- Since I Fell For You -- It's You -- Never Enough -- You Don't Know Me.
      Also performed by: David Sanborn.
    - Give Me the Night, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: HS 3453
      Love X Love -- Off Broadway -- Moody's Hood -- Give Me The Night -- What's On Your Mind -- Dinorah Dinorah -- Star Of A Story (x) -- Midnight Love Affair -- Turn Out The Lamplight.
    - Kenny Rogers: Greatest Hits, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: LOO-1072
      The Gambler -- Lucille -- Ruby -- Coward Of The County -- She Believes In Me -- You Decorated My Life -- Don't Fall In Love With A Dreamer -- Love The World Away -- Every Time Two Fools Collide -- Reuben James -- Long Arm Of The Law -- Lady.
    - Fiddler on the Roof, 1964; 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: LSO-1093
      Tradition -- Matchmaker, Matchmaker -- If I Were a Rich Man -- Sabbath Prayer -- To Life -- Miracle of Miracles -- Tevvey's Dream -- Sunrise, Sunset -- Now I Have Everything -- Do You Love Me? -- Far From the Home I Love -- Anatevka.
      Original Broadway cast recording.
    - Belafonte, 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: LPM-1150
      Waterboy -- Troubles -- Suzanne -- Matilda -- Take My Mother Home -- Noah -- Scarlet Ribbons -- In That Great Gettin' Up Mornin' -- Unchained Melody -- Jump Down, Spin Around -- Sylvie.
    - The Sound of Music, 1 12" sound disc (Box 174, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: LSOD-2005
      Prelude and the Sound of Music -- Maria -- Overture and Preludium -- Orchestra and Nuns Chorus -- I Have Confidence -- Maria -- Sixteen Going on Seventeen -- Rolf and Liesl -- My Favorite Things -- Maria -- Climb Ev'ry Mountain -- Mother Abbess -- The Lonely Goatherd -- Maria and the Children -- The Sound of Music -- The Children and the Captain -- Do-Re-Mi -- Maria and the Children -- Something Good -- Maria and the Captain -- Processional and Maria -- Organ, Orchestra and Nuns Chorus -- Edelweiss -- The Captain, Maria, the Children and Chorus -- So Long, Farewell -- The Children -- Climb Ev'ry Mountain (Reprise) -- Chorus and Orchestra.
    - New Piano In Town, 1961; 1 12" (Box 174, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: LSP-2383
      Stormy Weather -- Three Coins In The Fountian -- On The Street Where You Live -- Tea For Two -- On A Slow Boat To China -- Bess, You Is My Woman -- Body And Soul -- Mountain Greenery -- St. Louis Blues -- Long Ago And Far Away -- Maria -- Just One Of Those Things.
    - For The Nero-Minded, 1962; 1 12" (Box 174, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: LSP-2536
      Moon River -- Little Girl Blue -- Dancing On The Ceiling -- Isn't It Romantic -- My Man's Gone Now -- Everything I've Got -- Something's Coming -- Yesterdays -- Love Is A Simple Thing -- Too Late Now -- Let's Not Waste A Moment -- Don't Get Around Much Anymore.
    - The Pink Panther, 1963; 1 12" (Box 174, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: LSP-2795
      The Pink Panther Theme -- Champagne And Quail -- Royal Blue -- It Had Better Be Tonight -- The Village Inn -- Cortinal -- The Lonely Princess -- Something For Sellers -- Piano And Strings -- Shades Of Sennett.